<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<listings>
  <language>en</language>

  <listing>
    <id>16522</id>

    <name>82 Queen</name>

    <address format="simple">
      <component name="addr1">82 Queen Street</component>
      <component name="city">Charleston</component>
      <component name="postal_code">29401</component>
      <component name="province">SC</component>
    </address>

    <country>US</country>
    <latitude>32.777838</latitude>
    <longitude>-79.93242</longitude>

    <phone type="main">8437237591x</phone>

    <category>Low Country</category>
    <category>Seafood</category>
    <category>Southern</category>

    <date month="04" day="23" year="2015"/>
<content>
      <text>
        <link>http://www.opentable.com/rest_profile.aspx?rid=16522&amp;ref=7312</link>
        <title>82 Queen - Charleston</title>
<author>OpenTable.com</author>
        <body>82 Queen is the ultimate destination for a menu that is as diverse as Charleston. With it&apos;s lush garden outdoor seating and 11 elegant dining rooms, some of which are located upstairs. If this poses an issue, please be sure to let us know so we can plan your party accordingly. 82 Queen is also a beautiful embrace of intimate atmosphere and privacy. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From our famous She-Crab Soup, to Specialties of the House which include Southern Comfort BBQ Shrimp &amp; Grits, Pan Fried Low Country Crab cakes and Classic Fried Green Tomatoes, it?s no wonder 82 Queen continues to impress Southern Living Magazine as one of Charleston&apos;s finest, yet affordable dining establishments. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Open for over 30 years, 82 Queen continues to be the benchmark for Low country Cuisine and Southern Hospitality.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please also visit our other restaurants in the 82 Queen Restaurant Family, Lowcountry Bistro at LowcountryBistro.com and Swig and Swine at SwigAndSwineBBQ.com</body>
      <date month="04" day="23" year="2015"/>
</text>

      <review type="user">
        <link>http://www.opentable.com/rest_profile_reviews.aspx?rid=16522&amp;ref=7312</link>
        <title>82 Queen - Charleston</title>
<author>OpenTable.com</author>

        <rating name="Ambience">4.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Food">5.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Noise">3.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Overall">5.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Service">5.000000000000000</rating>

        <body>We started at the bar 30 mins before our reservation time. Very friendly &amp; enjoyable. The staff were very personable, came and got us for our reservation time. It&apos;s winter so the outdoor areas were closed off with heaters which all worked well. Had the she crab soup and it was outstanding.  Had the filet and it was perfect in every way. We will eat her again. Made the reservation on Open Table. That all worked perfectly.</body>
      <date month="04" day="23" year="2015"/>
</review>
      <review type="user">
        <link>http://www.opentable.com/rest_profile_reviews.aspx?rid=16522&amp;ref=7312</link>
        <title>82 Queen - Charleston</title>
<author>OpenTable.com</author>

        <rating name="Ambience">1.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Food">1.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Noise">2.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Overall">1.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Service">2.000000000000000</rating>

        <body>Very disappointed.  This restaurant was recommended by a friend and was not inexpensive.  First off, you go inside but are immediately taken back outside (into the cold) and upstairs to a back room.  Service was slow because of this and wait staff were all dressed in coats.  We were seated by the bus table with supply boxes visible in plain sight.  A special &quot;three olive&quot; salad was recommended by our server and came WITHOUT olives!  When this was mentioned, olives were brought out in a separate dish...no effort was made to replace or re-do the salad.  Salad was not taken off of the bill, either.  My wife&apos;s crab cake was simple and unappealing...presentation was poor.  My dish (a seafood ravioli concoction) was adequate but far from &quot;unique&quot;.    Altogether disappointing experience for a restaurant with it&apos;s price tag and &quot;reputation&quot;.  With so many other options in Charleston, we will not be returning.</body>
      <date month="04" day="23" year="2015"/>
</review>
      <review type="user">
        <link>http://www.opentable.com/rest_profile_reviews.aspx?rid=16522&amp;ref=7312</link>
        <title>82 Queen - Charleston</title>
<author>OpenTable.com</author>

        <rating name="Ambience">5.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Food">5.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Noise">3.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Overall">5.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Service">5.000000000000000</rating>

        <body>great reasturant!! the food and service was incredible. I have heard about this place for awhile and it definitely lived up to its expectations. cant wait to go back!!</body>
      <date month="04" day="23" year="2015"/>
</review>
      <review type="user">
        <link>http://www.opentable.com/rest_profile_reviews.aspx?rid=16522&amp;ref=7312</link>
        <title>82 Queen - Charleston</title>
<author>OpenTable.com</author>

        <rating name="Ambience">3.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Food">3.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Noise">3.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Overall">3.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Service">3.000000000000000</rating>

        <body>I wanted to love 82 Queen after it had been recommended to us as a nice historic spot. I went with my Mom and our meals were good but nothing was great about our overall meal. Maybe is was because we were there for lunch, but this won&apos;t make my short list when family comes to visit me as a must go restaurant.</body>
      <date month="04" day="23" year="2015"/>
</review>
      <review type="user">
        <link>http://www.opentable.com/rest_profile_reviews.aspx?rid=16522&amp;ref=7312</link>
        <title>82 Queen - Charleston</title>
<author>OpenTable.com</author>

        <rating name="Ambience">4.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Food">2.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Noise">2.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Overall">2.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Service">4.000000000000000</rating>

        <body>Very beautiful spot and the server was very nice. Had the prime rib. It was thin and dry and overlooked. With all the great restuarants in charleston Id say pass on this one. You can do much better.  Very expensive</body>
      <date month="04" day="23" year="2015"/>
</review>
      <review type="user">
        <link>http://www.opentable.com/rest_profile_reviews.aspx?rid=16522&amp;ref=7312</link>
        <title>82 Queen - Charleston</title>
<author>OpenTable.com</author>

        <rating name="Ambience">4.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Food">5.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Noise">2.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Overall">4.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Service">5.000000000000000</rating>

        <body>Our waitress Molly was great and the food was superb, There was a loud large party in the next room, but they shut the doors which we appreciated. I thought the music could be more mellow-don&apos;t know if it was piped music, but was too &quot;rocky:&quot; Molly did turn it down so we could hold a conversation. All in all a great experience.</body>
      <date month="04" day="23" year="2015"/>
</review>
      <review type="user">
        <link>http://www.opentable.com/rest_profile_reviews.aspx?rid=16522&amp;ref=7312</link>
        <title>82 Queen - Charleston</title>
<author>OpenTable.com</author>

        <rating name="Ambience">5.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Food">5.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Noise">1.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Overall">5.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Service">5.000000000000000</rating>

        <body>We went here on a recomendation at the last minute.  This place is unassuming, quiet, small, intimate, and quite a find!  As appetizers, we had the recommended She-Crab Soup (DELICIOUS!!!) and the Fried Green Tomatoes (also DELICIOUS!!).  As entrees, I tried the Duo of Duck (for the first time because our server told me that it was NOT greasy the way 82 Queen did it -- and if I didn&apos;t like it, they would make it right with whatever I wanted).  The dish consisted of sliced duck breast and a confit with the duck leg and thigh.  This was served with a bing cherry compote and served with mashed root vegetables.  This dish was outrageous!  I absolutely loved it!.  Our other entree was the Carolina Crab Cakes; these cakes had no discernable filler, were huge, and were made with sweet, tender crab and lightly fried.  For dessert, we had the bourbon pecan pie with vanilla ice cream and the lemon chiffon cake.  YUM!  We&apos;re from New York and have eaten at many fabulous restaurants, but 82 Queen</body>
      <date month="04" day="23" year="2015"/>
</review>
      <review type="user">
        <link>http://www.opentable.com/rest_profile_reviews.aspx?rid=16522&amp;ref=7312</link>
        <title>82 Queen - Charleston</title>
<author>OpenTable.com</author>

        <rating name="Ambience">4.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Food">5.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Noise">1.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Overall">5.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Service">5.000000000000000</rating>

        <body>Warm cosy attentive service</body>
      <date month="04" day="23" year="2015"/>
</review>
      <review type="user">
        <link>http://www.opentable.com/rest_profile_reviews.aspx?rid=16522&amp;ref=7312</link>
        <title>82 Queen - Charleston</title>
<author>OpenTable.com</author>

        <rating name="Ambience">5.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Food">5.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Noise">1.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Overall">5.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Service">5.000000000000000</rating>

        <body>With all of the superb restaurants in Charleston, SC, it was hard to know where to eat with only two nights in this gem of a town. The recommendation that came from our tour guide, other hotel guests and our hotel management was 82 Queen.  Now, I would like to recommend the place to your readers. It is a lovely place, quiet and romantic without being stodgy. The chef is brilliant and the servers are professional. We ate outside in the courtyard and it was enchanting. If you only have a handful of nights in Charleston, you must dine here.</body>
      <date month="04" day="23" year="2015"/>
</review>
      <review type="user">
        <link>http://www.opentable.com/rest_profile_reviews.aspx?rid=16522&amp;ref=7312</link>
        <title>82 Queen - Charleston</title>
<author>OpenTable.com</author>

        <rating name="Ambience">5.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Food">4.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Noise">3.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Overall">4.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Service">5.000000000000000</rating>

        <body>82 Queen is an elegant place, the courtyard is quite and pleasant to eat in.  The staff is great and the good was fantastic.  This is a must visit when in Charleston, the food and atmosphere is Charleston.</body>
      <date month="04" day="23" year="2015"/>
</review>
      <review type="user">
        <link>http://www.opentable.com/rest_profile_reviews.aspx?rid=16522&amp;ref=7312</link>
        <title>82 Queen - Charleston</title>
<author>OpenTable.com</author>

        <rating name="Ambience">5.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Food">5.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Noise">2.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Overall">5.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Service">5.000000000000000</rating>

        <body>We thoroughly enjoyed our Restaurant Week visit to 82 Queen.  Their fried green tomatoes are the best!  We enjoyed our entrees, and the lemoncello cake was a perfect finish to a perfect dining experience.</body>
      <date month="04" day="23" year="2015"/>
</review>
      <review type="user">
        <link>http://www.opentable.com/rest_profile_reviews.aspx?rid=16522&amp;ref=7312</link>
        <title>82 Queen - Charleston</title>
<author>OpenTable.com</author>

        <rating name="Ambience">5.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Food">4.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Noise">4.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Overall">5.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Service">5.000000000000000</rating>

        <body>The food was delicious but the service was outstanding!  Our server was Zack and he was knowledgable about all of the selections, as well as wine pairings. He was very responsive and extremely courteous! It is such a joy to have such  an enjoyable dining experience! We will definitely be back!</body>
      <date month="04" day="23" year="2015"/>
</review>
      <review type="user">
        <link>http://www.opentable.com/rest_profile_reviews.aspx?rid=16522&amp;ref=7312</link>
        <title>82 Queen - Charleston</title>
<author>OpenTable.com</author>

        <rating name="Ambience">5.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Food">5.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Noise">3.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Overall">5.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Service">5.000000000000000</rating>

        <body>Took a friend here for lunch as a birthday present, but we both received the gift of an excellent meal and friendly service in a charming ambiance.  This was probably my 4th time coming here and I&apos;m never disappointed, but I was wowed this time.  The food was outstanding. Started out with baked Brie with soft pretzels served warm out of the oven. The sweet potatoe mustard was unique and helped to make this so delicious. Then had a great stacked turkey sandwich that came with homemade chips. Oh, but the best part was the chocolate lava cake with raspberry sauce. I took half my sandwich home with me just so I could have room for this dessert. Yum.  Really enjoyed coming here, but I must say don&apos;t expect to eat a quick meal.  But then again it was truly nice to take our time, talk, enjoy our surroundings, and have great food.</body>
      <date month="04" day="23" year="2015"/>
</review>
      <review type="user">
        <link>http://www.opentable.com/rest_profile_reviews.aspx?rid=16522&amp;ref=7312</link>
        <title>82 Queen - Charleston</title>
<author>OpenTable.com</author>

        <rating name="Ambience">3.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Food">3.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Noise">2.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Overall">3.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Service">2.000000000000000</rating>

        <body>I&apos;ve been there once before the other night and thoroughly enjoyed it the first time but this second time I visited for restaurant week, I didn&apos;t enjoy it nearly as much.</body>
      <date month="04" day="23" year="2015"/>
</review>
      <review type="user">
        <link>http://www.opentable.com/rest_profile_reviews.aspx?rid=16522&amp;ref=7312</link>
        <title>82 Queen - Charleston</title>
<author>OpenTable.com</author>

        <rating name="Ambience">5.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Food">4.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Noise">1.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Overall">5.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Service">4.000000000000000</rating>

        <body>Our sister recommended this restaurant, which turned out to be just doors down from our hotel.  The food lived up to the recommendation.  My wife loved her Jambalaya; my fried chicken with collard greens was also very good.  Our table was in a very pretty room, well lit room.  The ambience was casually elegant and very cheerful.  We very much enjoyed our meal at 82 Queen Street.</body>
      <date month="04" day="23" year="2015"/>
</review>
      <review type="user">
        <link>http://www.opentable.com/rest_profile_reviews.aspx?rid=16522&amp;ref=7312</link>
        <title>82 Queen - Charleston</title>
<author>OpenTable.com</author>

        <rating name="Ambience">3.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Food">5.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Noise">3.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Overall">4.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Service">4.000000000000000</rating>

        <body>Great food and near fine dining experience. Impressive large portions for the cost. Shea crab soup, beets salad crab cakes and gumbo recommended from this visit. All lowcountry classics and favorite dishes and sides available.  Reservations recommended but not sure why they sat another party next to our table so early in the evening when the restaurant was still sort of empty at 6pm. Other than that everything was great. They gave us a nice corner convenient for bringing an 8 month old baby with us.</body>
      <date month="04" day="23" year="2015"/>
</review>
      <review type="user">
        <link>http://www.opentable.com/rest_profile_reviews.aspx?rid=16522&amp;ref=7312</link>
        <title>82 Queen - Charleston</title>
<author>OpenTable.com</author>

        <rating name="Ambience">4.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Food">4.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Noise">4.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Overall">4.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Service">5.000000000000000</rating>

        <body>This is not the first time I have visited 82 Queen, and we were not disappointed on a brunch visit last Saturday with a party of 4.  The weather precluded sitting outside, but the patio area had been enclosed and heated and so we almost got the impression that we were sitting outside.  The food and service were good.  We will be back.</body>
      <date month="04" day="23" year="2015"/>
</review>
      <review type="user">
        <link>http://www.opentable.com/rest_profile_reviews.aspx?rid=16522&amp;ref=7312</link>
        <title>82 Queen - Charleston</title>
<author>OpenTable.com</author>

        <rating name="Ambience">4.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Food">5.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Noise">2.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Overall">5.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Service">5.000000000000000</rating>

        <body>This is a long time favorite restaurant of mine especially for their crab cakes. I had not been there for about 15 years and the crabcakes were a disappointment but she crab soup was outstanding.   They are all crab meat  but not the fresh lump crab  I was expecting.</body>
      <date month="04" day="23" year="2015"/>
</review>
      <review type="user">
        <link>http://www.opentable.com/rest_profile_reviews.aspx?rid=16522&amp;ref=7312</link>
        <title>82 Queen - Charleston</title>
<author>OpenTable.com</author>

        <rating name="Ambience">4.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Food">3.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Noise">3.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Overall">4.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Service">5.000000000000000</rating>

        <body>We went on a date night for Restaurant Week.  The 3 for $30 menu was a great deal.  The she-crab soup was excellent, along with the fried green tomatoes. We both had the filet and they were cooked perfectly.  Too many peppercorns, but the Bloody Mary sauce was excellent.  Desserts were ok.  Overall, an enjoyable night.</body>
      <date month="04" day="23" year="2015"/>
</review>
      <review type="user">
        <link>http://www.opentable.com/rest_profile_reviews.aspx?rid=16522&amp;ref=7312</link>
        <title>82 Queen - Charleston</title>
<author>OpenTable.com</author>

        <rating name="Ambience">5.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Food">5.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Noise">1.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Overall">5.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Service">5.000000000000000</rating>

        <body>Food and service were outstanding.  Always make a point of visiting 82 Queen when in Charleston.  Ambience is charming.</body>
      <date month="04" day="23" year="2015"/>
</review>
      <review type="user">
        <link>http://www.opentable.com/rest_profile_reviews.aspx?rid=16522&amp;ref=7312</link>
        <title>82 Queen - Charleston</title>
<author>OpenTable.com</author>

        <rating name="Ambience">3.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Food">1.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Noise">3.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Overall">2.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Service">2.000000000000000</rating>

        <body>she crab was so bad . i was shocked i have been coming since the restaurant opened i ordered pork osso bucco that was good but everything on the plate was cold. pimento cheese balls were not done in the middle staff did not seem to care if we were happy or not</body>
      <date month="04" day="23" year="2015"/>
</review>
      <review type="user">
        <link>http://www.opentable.com/rest_profile_reviews.aspx?rid=16522&amp;ref=7312</link>
        <title>82 Queen - Charleston</title>
<author>OpenTable.com</author>

        <rating name="Ambience">4.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Food">4.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Noise">1.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Overall">4.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Service">4.000000000000000</rating>

        <body>enjoyed our brunch very much.  Service was a bit slow, but overall very good.  Food was good, staff all very friendly.</body>
      <date month="04" day="23" year="2015"/>
</review>
      <review type="user">
        <link>http://www.opentable.com/rest_profile_reviews.aspx?rid=16522&amp;ref=7312</link>
        <title>82 Queen - Charleston</title>
<author>OpenTable.com</author>

        <rating name="Ambience">5.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Food">4.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Noise">3.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Overall">5.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Service">5.000000000000000</rating>

        <body>Each time I visit I have a lovely experience. I recommend this restaurant to anyone who is just looking for a great environment to eat in the downtown Charleston area. The atmosphere is very pleasant and the staff members are welcoming. I try something different and each dish brings about a taste that is unimaginable.</body>
      <date month="04" day="23" year="2015"/>
</review>
      <review type="user">
        <link>http://www.opentable.com/rest_profile_reviews.aspx?rid=16522&amp;ref=7312</link>
        <title>82 Queen - Charleston</title>
<author>OpenTable.com</author>

        <rating name="Ambience">1.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Food">1.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Noise">1.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Overall">1.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Service">1.000000000000000</rating>

        <body>The service was slow and food was cold. The wine ordered for dinner was served after the entire was almost over. The manager and waitress offered to adjust the bill for the poor service but the bill was finally never adjusted. The dining room we were seated was away from the kitchen and bathrooms and had absolutely no ambiance - felt like we were seated on an outside covered porch and on a cold day it was not very comfortable</body>
      <date month="04" day="23" year="2015"/>
</review>
      <review type="user">
        <link>http://www.opentable.com/rest_profile_reviews.aspx?rid=16522&amp;ref=7312</link>
        <title>82 Queen - Charleston</title>
<author>OpenTable.com</author>

        <rating name="Ambience">1.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Food">3.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Noise">2.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Overall">2.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Service">4.000000000000000</rating>

        <body>A once majestic restaurant that sorely needs an update.</body>
      <date month="04" day="23" year="2015"/>
</review>
      <review type="user">
        <link>http://www.opentable.com/rest_profile_reviews.aspx?rid=16522&amp;ref=7312</link>
        <title>82 Queen - Charleston</title>
<author>OpenTable.com</author>

        <rating name="Ambience">3.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Food">3.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Noise">2.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Overall">3.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Service">2.000000000000000</rating>

        <body>We arrived on a wet evening. We  had an early dinner reservation as we were told that 6 pm was all that was left, they were so full. When we got there the two rooms in the particular building we were in had a noisy group in one and  only  another couple in ours which had five tables. We were  quickly taken care of. I ordered Jambalaya which is the signature meal. Pictures of it on the net did not match the dish I got. It was a red pile of rice in a piquant sauce with about 6 nice sized shrimp on top. I found no craw fish, peppers, or other ingredients. It was tasty  but looked more like porridge! So I was disappointed with the presentation which for 26 $ was more rice than anything else. So it was way OVER priced. My husband had pork. It was very dry, nothing special either. We asked for bottle water which took forever to arrive. Your dessert choices were very weak, all very sweet so not to our taste. It seems that the chef prepared  all meals  ahead as well  to speed up service so we</body>
      <date month="04" day="23" year="2015"/>
</review>
      <review type="user">
        <link>http://www.opentable.com/rest_profile_reviews.aspx?rid=16522&amp;ref=7312</link>
        <title>82 Queen - Charleston</title>
<author>OpenTable.com</author>

        <rating name="Ambience">4.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Food">1.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Noise">3.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Overall">2.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Service">5.000000000000000</rating>

        <body>I have eaten here several times over the years, and this was another birthday celebration with parents in from out of town.  We were all looking forward to the dinner.  Soup and salad were great but when the dinner came, we were overcome with salt!  3 of us had fish dishes and my husband had a steak.  The steak was great; however, the potatoes were a little undercooked.  To spend that amount of money and walk out of there disappointed is, well, disappointing.  It will probably be a while before we give it another shot.</body>
      <date month="04" day="23" year="2015"/>
</review>
      <review type="user">
        <link>http://www.opentable.com/rest_profile_reviews.aspx?rid=16522&amp;ref=7312</link>
        <title>82 Queen - Charleston</title>
<author>OpenTable.com</author>

        <rating name="Ambience">2.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Food">2.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Noise">1.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Overall">2.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Service">2.000000000000000</rating>

        <body>We were very disappointed......Fried greens tomatoes were greasy and rather tasteless, fried chicken was dry. Maybe it was a bad day of the week? we had dinner on Monday night.  My Salmon had a big blob of butter on top, not  needed but salmon was unremarkable. others in our party had the shrimp and grits and enjoyed the dish but again not remarkable.  Server was pleasant enough but not very attentive nor responsive.  We wont go again.</body>
      <date month="04" day="23" year="2015"/>
</review>
      <review type="user">
        <link>http://www.opentable.com/rest_profile_reviews.aspx?rid=16522&amp;ref=7312</link>
        <title>82 Queen - Charleston</title>
<author>OpenTable.com</author>

        <rating name="Ambience">5.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Food">3.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Noise">4.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Overall">3.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Service">3.000000000000000</rating>

        <body>I have been here several times as a local.. This time we took out of town guest for lunch and were disappointed. The time between courses was very long and my brother in law&apos;s shrimp and grits was luke warm. I realize it was very cold outside and the food needed to be brought in from another building but... too bad. Our courses took forever. We really enjoyed the she crab soup and baked brie but we kind of got bored waiting for the main course and then desert. The place was not busy so there was not really any reason for that much of a delay.</body>
      <date month="04" day="23" year="2015"/>
</review>
      <review type="user">
        <link>http://www.opentable.com/rest_profile_reviews.aspx?rid=16522&amp;ref=7312</link>
        <title>82 Queen - Charleston</title>
<author>OpenTable.com</author>

        <rating name="Ambience">5.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Food">5.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Noise">3.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Overall">5.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Service">5.000000000000000</rating>

        <body>As a couple that likes to get away and seek special little &quot;finds &quot;, 82 Queen was such a delight! Our waiter was very knowledgeable and we enjoyed his recommendations and wine trivia. The food was delicious and the atmosphere was peaceful and romantic.</body>
      <date month="04" day="23" year="2015"/>
</review>
      <review type="user">
        <link>http://www.opentable.com/rest_profile_reviews.aspx?rid=16522&amp;ref=7312</link>
        <title>82 Queen - Charleston</title>
<author>OpenTable.com</author>

        <rating name="Ambience">5.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Food">2.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Noise">3.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Overall">3.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Service">5.000000000000000</rating>

        <body>We had recommendations from a relative that we should definitely eat here as it was one of her favorite spots when visiting Charleston.  We had lunch there and were just a bit disappointed.  I had the turkey sandwich.  The bread seemed stale and very dry.  My husband had the Southern Cheeseburger and the same was true for his sandwich.  The redeeming aspect of the meal for both of us was the kale salad.  Our waiter was great and promptly serviced our every need.</body>
      <date month="04" day="23" year="2015"/>
</review>
      <review type="user">
        <link>http://www.opentable.com/rest_profile_reviews.aspx?rid=16522&amp;ref=7312</link>
        <title>82 Queen - Charleston</title>
<author>OpenTable.com</author>

        <rating name="Ambience">2.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Food">1.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Noise">3.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Overall">1.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Service">2.000000000000000</rating>

        <body>We had dinner at 82 Queen on New Year&apos;s day in the early evening.  AT first take the restaurant appears very friendly and inviting.  And the drinks were respectable.  After the drinks, however, the evening went downhill fast.  To be brief, the fried brie was cold in the middle,  Accompanying the cold brie were two smears of stuff, one was a red overspiced apple type sauce and another larger smear of a cold sweet potato/squash thing.  This presentation should have been an embarrassment to this establishment.  I had an acceptable pork chop with  greens that were luke warm at best (ok taste but clearly not recently cooked) and a cool sweet potato cake (I think).  Perhaps because it was New Years day we shouldn&apos;t have had reasonable expectations?  Not!!!  If I am going to experience a &quot;C&quot; team presentation then I should pay &quot;C&quot; team prices.  I sincerely hope this very pleasant spot is able to pull their act together but whatever they attempt will have to be after a very comprehensive kitc</body>
      <date month="04" day="23" year="2015"/>
</review>
      <review type="user">
        <link>http://www.opentable.com/rest_profile_reviews.aspx?rid=16522&amp;ref=7312</link>
        <title>82 Queen - Charleston</title>
<author>OpenTable.com</author>

        <rating name="Ambience">5.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Food">5.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Noise">1.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Overall">5.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Service">5.000000000000000</rating>

        <body>This was our first visit to 82 Queen but will not be our last.  We arrived early for our reservation and enjoyed a delicious cocktail at the bar.  The bar tenders were well versed on the liquor choices. Our dinner was delicious and the service was friendly and professional.  We dined on the soft shell crab special and the crab cakes entree.  Both were excellent.</body>
      <date month="04" day="23" year="2015"/>
</review>
      <review type="user">
        <link>http://www.opentable.com/rest_profile_reviews.aspx?rid=16522&amp;ref=7312</link>
        <title>82 Queen - Charleston</title>
<author>OpenTable.com</author>

        <rating name="Ambience">5.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Food">5.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Noise">3.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Overall">5.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Service">5.000000000000000</rating>

        <body>We have enjoyed dining at 82 Queen on several past trips to Charleston, and were fortunate to be there during restaurant week this year.   The special menu choices were excellent, with portions much larger than we expected during a special promotion - no different than their regular menu sizes.    Absolutely the best crab cakes and she crab soup in Charleston!  The service is above excellent.  I highly recommend 82 Queen.</body>
      <date month="04" day="23" year="2015"/>
</review>
      <review type="user">
        <link>http://www.opentable.com/rest_profile_reviews.aspx?rid=16522&amp;ref=7312</link>
        <title>82 Queen - Charleston</title>
<author>OpenTable.com</author>

        <rating name="Ambience">5.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Food">5.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Noise">1.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Overall">5.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Service">5.000000000000000</rating>

        <body>Quaint, old and very southern feel to the architecture.  Food was excellent as well as the service. The wine list was extensive and the selections were very well described. Great date location.</body>
      <date month="04" day="23" year="2015"/>
</review>
      <review type="user">
        <link>http://www.opentable.com/rest_profile_reviews.aspx?rid=16522&amp;ref=7312</link>
        <title>82 Queen - Charleston</title>
<author>OpenTable.com</author>

        <rating name="Ambience">3.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Food">1.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Noise">2.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Overall">3.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Service">3.000000000000000</rating>

        <body>We have always enjoyed our visits to 82 Queen and hate that this go around was not one of those wonderful visits. My fried chicken thigh was overcooked and tough so I had to send it back and the second go around, the chicken was tasteless and the &quot;garlic mashed potatoes&quot; tasted like they didn&apos;t even have salt let alone any garlic. My husband also stated that they had changed the shrimp and grits as it was now chunkier yellow grits and smaller portions. They did comp my food which I appreciated since I didn&apos;t even end up eating it however, I don&apos;t believe it will be worth another visit. It&apos;s a shame because we always look forward to a nice meal downtown.</body>
      <date month="04" day="23" year="2015"/>
</review>
      <review type="user">
        <link>http://www.opentable.com/rest_profile_reviews.aspx?rid=16522&amp;ref=7312</link>
        <title>82 Queen - Charleston</title>
<author>OpenTable.com</author>

        <rating name="Ambience">4.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Food">4.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Noise">4.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Overall">4.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Service">4.000000000000000</rating>

        <body>I had a fun evening at 82 Queen.  I chose the Oysters and classic shrimp &amp; grits along with a light and tasty lemon cake for dessert.  All in all, I had a nice meal and enjoyable time.</body>
      <date month="04" day="23" year="2015"/>
</review>
      <review type="user">
        <link>http://www.opentable.com/rest_profile_reviews.aspx?rid=16522&amp;ref=7312</link>
        <title>82 Queen - Charleston</title>
<author>OpenTable.com</author>

        <rating name="Ambience">5.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Food">5.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Noise">2.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Overall">5.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Service">5.000000000000000</rating>

        <body>Outdoor seating is so beautiful, the staff is friendly and the food is awesome...I had never tasted fried green tomatoes or grits, and now am spoiled as I haven&apos;t tasted better anywhere...the grits with the barbecued shrimp were so creamy and delicious.....I&apos;m glad I had my first taste here!!!</body>
      <date month="04" day="23" year="2015"/>
</review>
      <review type="user">
        <link>http://www.opentable.com/rest_profile_reviews.aspx?rid=16522&amp;ref=7312</link>
        <title>82 Queen - Charleston</title>
<author>OpenTable.com</author>

        <rating name="Ambience">5.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Food">5.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Noise">3.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Overall">5.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Service">5.000000000000000</rating>

        <body>My wife and I were visiting Charleston from New Orleans.  We were directed to 82 Queen for a classic Charleston dinner and the restaurant did not disappoint.  We stayed with classic dishes such as the She Crab Soup and Shrimp &amp; Grits.  As a native New Orleanian, the Shrimp &amp; Grits were as good as any I&apos;ve had.  The service and ambiance were fantastic.  Overall, we had an outstanding meal and look forward to returning when we&apos;re back in Charleston.</body>
      <date month="04" day="23" year="2015"/>
</review>
      <review type="user">
        <link>http://www.opentable.com/rest_profile_reviews.aspx?rid=16522&amp;ref=7312</link>
        <title>82 Queen - Charleston</title>
<author>OpenTable.com</author>

        <rating name="Ambience">5.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Food">5.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Noise">2.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Overall">5.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Service">5.000000000000000</rating>

        <body>My wife and I went to 82 Queen on the evening of New Years Day. We were pleased that they were open. We were seated in the Library. Our server, Chcuk, was an absolute delight. He was very helpful in accomodating my wife&apos;s food allergies, and he made spot on suggestions for items on the menu. I enjoyed the She Crab Soup and Shrimp and Grits and my wife had grilled salmon and sauted spinach. The room only had about 5 tables, and all were occupied. Chucck methodically worked all 5 and the result was a happy and satisfied room. Our dinner was leisurely, and we left very satisfied.</body>
      <date month="04" day="23" year="2015"/>
</review>
      <review type="user">
        <link>http://www.opentable.com/rest_profile_reviews.aspx?rid=16522&amp;ref=7312</link>
        <title>82 Queen - Charleston</title>
<author>OpenTable.com</author>

        <rating name="Ambience">5.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Food">3.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Noise">2.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Overall">3.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Service">4.000000000000000</rating>

        <body>This is a great place to dine outdoors.  The trees and setting are lovely.  The food is good but not outstanding.  I would recommend the ambiance but it&apos;s more of a touristy place than an exceptional dining experience.</body>
      <date month="04" day="23" year="2015"/>
</review>
      <review type="user">
        <link>http://www.opentable.com/rest_profile_reviews.aspx?rid=16522&amp;ref=7312</link>
        <title>82 Queen - Charleston</title>
<author>OpenTable.com</author>

        <rating name="Ambience">5.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Food">5.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Noise">1.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Overall">5.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Service">5.000000000000000</rating>

        <body>Been here many times, never dissoppointed. Barbecue shrimp &amp; grits was the best I have ever tasted. Truly special. The pimento cheese on the fried green tomatoes was also really special. The food really has lots of flavor and it is obvious there is a very discerning chef and staff in the back ensuring that the quality of the food is top notch.   The atmosphere here is beautiful. There is a Spanish garden in the middle of the restaurant and dining there is  very relaxing.  One of my favorites. We come here again and again.</body>
      <date month="04" day="23" year="2015"/>
</review>
      <review type="user">
        <link>http://www.opentable.com/rest_profile_reviews.aspx?rid=16522&amp;ref=7312</link>
        <title>82 Queen - Charleston</title>
<author>OpenTable.com</author>

        <rating name="Ambience">4.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Food">5.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Noise">4.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Overall">4.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Service">2.000000000000000</rating>

        <body>Our food was excellent, generous portions, beautifully presented. But the service was so uneven. We waited at least 20 minutes until we actually had drinks, the soup then came immediately before we even had time to sip our cocktails. Then there was another huge gap waiting for entres and the long promised fesh bread only appeared after the entres were served. Hard time getting a second drink and post meal coffee......just made what could have been an excellent meal seem like a bit of an ordeal.....</body>
      <date month="04" day="23" year="2015"/>
</review>
      <review type="user">
        <link>http://www.opentable.com/rest_profile_reviews.aspx?rid=16522&amp;ref=7312</link>
        <title>82 Queen - Charleston</title>
<author>OpenTable.com</author>

        <rating name="Ambience">2.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Food">2.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Noise">2.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Overall">2.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Service">2.000000000000000</rating>

        <body>This was our second visit to 82 Queen, our first was last May during graduation week in Charleston. The first time was &quot;enjoyable&quot;, last week was not particularly for the price point. I had chicken stuffed with crab, lemon tarragon white rice and asparagus. The chicken was dry and overdone, the rice was very tacky with little flavor. The best part was the asparagus.</body>
      <date month="04" day="23" year="2015"/>
</review>
      <review type="user">
        <link>http://www.opentable.com/rest_profile_reviews.aspx?rid=16522&amp;ref=7312</link>
        <title>82 Queen - Charleston</title>
<author>OpenTable.com</author>

        <rating name="Ambience">5.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Food">5.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Noise">2.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Overall">5.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Service">5.000000000000000</rating>

        <body>Whenever in Charleston, we always have at meal at 82 Queen and are never disappointed.  Love tbe outside seating!</body>
      <date month="04" day="23" year="2015"/>
</review>
      <review type="user">
        <link>http://www.opentable.com/rest_profile_reviews.aspx?rid=16522&amp;ref=7312</link>
        <title>82 Queen - Charleston</title>
<author>OpenTable.com</author>

        <rating name="Ambience">2.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Food">2.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Noise">2.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Overall">2.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Service">2.000000000000000</rating>

        <body>This was our only disappointing dining experience in our week in South Carolina.  We ate out 3 days and nights in Greenville and 4 days and nights in Charleston. The food was mediocre.  All of our dishes were okay.  The service from hostess to waiters was mediocre.  This is not a restaurant to which I would return or recommend to others.  The restaurant is reviewed favorably in many places, but it is riding on its laurels.  Too many other wonderful places to eat.  82 Queen is not hungry to be great.</body>
      <date month="04" day="23" year="2015"/>
</review>
      <review type="user">
        <link>http://www.opentable.com/rest_profile_reviews.aspx?rid=16522&amp;ref=7312</link>
        <title>82 Queen - Charleston</title>
<author>OpenTable.com</author>

        <rating name="Ambience">5.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Food">5.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Noise">1.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Overall">5.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Service">5.000000000000000</rating>

        <body>This restaurant is a Charleston landmark.  The food is consistently wonderful.  The restaurant is a great place for a romantic evening or just a quiet time with Friends.   Parking is easy right across the street in the garage.   Great atmospere and trulu Charleston.  Be sure to try the shrimp and grits.  The pecan pie is homemade also.  Yum</body>
      <date month="04" day="23" year="2015"/>
</review>
      <review type="user">
        <link>http://www.opentable.com/rest_profile_reviews.aspx?rid=16522&amp;ref=7312</link>
        <title>82 Queen - Charleston</title>
<author>OpenTable.com</author>

        <rating name="Ambience">4.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Food">1.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Noise">2.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Overall">2.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Service">2.000000000000000</rating>

        <body>We tried several restaurants during our stay in Charleston. We were very excited about this restaurant because we were told by several people to try it. However, just like the reviews I&apos;ve read in other places the restaurant seems to be riding on it&apos;s old reviews. Out of all the restaurants we dined in this is the only one I would never return to. Our server was friendly but very inattentive. He had too much to handle. The food was completely unsatisfying. I have tried shrimp and grits and each restaurant we have eaten at and this was the only place where it was dry and pasty like glue. My dining partner it had the jambalaya and dryness was the same problem. The shrimp and both dishes work so overcooked they were chewy and rubbery. I always try to find something positive to say about a place so this is what I will say… The atmosphere is very nice and the complementary cheese biscuits are delicious! But that is not enough to bring me back to any restaurant.</body>
      <date month="04" day="23" year="2015"/>
</review>
      <review type="user">
        <link>http://www.opentable.com/rest_profile_reviews.aspx?rid=16522&amp;ref=7312</link>
        <title>82 Queen - Charleston</title>
<author>OpenTable.com</author>

        <rating name="Ambience">5.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Food">5.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Noise">1.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Overall">5.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Service">5.000000000000000</rating>

        <body>Its been about 30 years since I visited 82 Queen because I moved out of the area. I was so glad I went back. We did lunch there and I was reminded that the Charleston She Crab soup is the best I&apos;ve ever had. I love that they bring it and tell you to give the sherry a stir because its still floating on top. I won&apos;t wait another 30 years to come back I promise.</body>
      <date month="04" day="23" year="2015"/>
</review>
      <review type="user">
        <link>http://www.opentable.com/rest_profile_reviews.aspx?rid=16522&amp;ref=7312</link>
        <title>82 Queen - Charleston</title>
<author>OpenTable.com</author>

        <rating name="Ambience">5.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Food">5.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Noise">1.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Overall">5.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Service">5.000000000000000</rating>

        <body>Great outdoor dining with outstanding service.  The fried green tomatoes were scrumptious!  I want a bucket of the pimiento cheese and a gallon of the bacon marmalade.  French pork chop was well cooked, tender and flavorful.  Loved the sweet potato mash, and the spinach was cooked just right.  Enjoyed the staff and the courtyard.  A great touch of Charleston.</body>
      <date month="04" day="23" year="2015"/>
</review>
      <review type="user">
        <link>http://www.opentable.com/rest_profile_reviews.aspx?rid=16522&amp;ref=7312</link>
        <title>82 Queen - Charleston</title>
<author>OpenTable.com</author>

        <rating name="Ambience">3.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Food">2.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Noise">4.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Overall">3.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Service">2.000000000000000</rating>

        <body>Made reservation for resturant week.  I have eaten there before and found it much better when it wasn&apos;t resturant week. Rainy night but they had us walk all the way to the back of the resturant and up slippery outside stairs.  Our waiter was friendly enough but seemed to miss a few things like the bread and butter--it never showed up even after a few requests.  My guest had the pork dish which was fantastic.  The portion was large and the taste was great.  Highly recommend it.  I had the filet and it was very disappointing .  The portion was very small and tough--perhaps a smaller plate would help it may not not look so lost on the plate. Tables by the windows were very close and the table behind us kept hitting our chairs.  All in all not so great experience.</body>
      <date month="04" day="23" year="2015"/>
</review>
      <review type="user">
        <link>http://www.opentable.com/rest_profile_reviews.aspx?rid=16522&amp;ref=7312</link>
        <title>82 Queen - Charleston</title>
<author>OpenTable.com</author>

        <rating name="Ambience">5.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Food">4.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Noise">4.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Overall">4.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Service">4.000000000000000</rating>

        <body>Started well at the bar waiting for our table. Vodka martini was ample with choice of vodka. Good selection of wines by the glass for my wife. As is customary in Charleston, the resturant offered a special New Year&apos;s menu. Lamb chops were excellent as was the turf portion (filet mignon) of &quot;land &amp; sea.&quot; The lobster tail might have benefited from a sauce but was certainly acceptable. A shared dessert and fresh coffee ended this enjoyable experience. This is not our first visit to 82 Queen and will not be the last due to the consistency, ambiance and good service.</body>
      <date month="04" day="23" year="2015"/>
</review>
      <review type="user">
        <link>http://www.opentable.com/rest_profile_reviews.aspx?rid=16522&amp;ref=7312</link>
        <title>82 Queen - Charleston</title>
<author>OpenTable.com</author>

        <rating name="Ambience">1.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Food">5.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Noise">2.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Overall">3.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Service">4.000000000000000</rating>

        <body>even thought the reservation was made 1 1/2 months in advance, we were seated at a table beside a storage room and a wait staff hub.  Way too much activity in and out of the room and imagine trying to have a romantic Valentines dinner with the wait staff constantly loading and unloading dirty &amp; clean plates 2 feet from you.  the location and staff activity totally ruined our evening</body>
      <date month="04" day="23" year="2015"/>
</review>
      <review type="user">
        <link>http://www.opentable.com/rest_profile_reviews.aspx?rid=16522&amp;ref=7312</link>
        <title>82 Queen - Charleston</title>
<author>OpenTable.com</author>

        <rating name="Ambience">5.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Food">5.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Noise">1.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Overall">5.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Service">5.000000000000000</rating>

        <body>The food was delicious,  cooked as ordered and service was at a pace that let us enjoy our meal but never once did we wait for service.  Our waiter was very attentive but not intrusive.  Wine suggestion was spot on for our meal.</body>
      <date month="04" day="23" year="2015"/>
</review>
      <review type="user">
        <link>http://www.opentable.com/rest_profile_reviews.aspx?rid=16522&amp;ref=7312</link>
        <title>82 Queen - Charleston</title>
<author>OpenTable.com</author>

        <rating name="Ambience">3.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Food">3.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Noise">1.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Overall">4.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Service">5.000000000000000</rating>

        <body>It was a beautiful night and we made reservations weeks ahead.  Lots of areas within the restaurant that are beautiful, but we were put at table &quot;301&quot;.  It was upstairs on the 3rd floor with a table much too small for a meal with bread basket and wine glasses. I did not ask for a picture to be taken of us because all of the lighting, music, and air controls were beside us and would be our background. The waiters were excellent.  Welcoming, professional, and efficient.  She-crab soup was divine!! Great pecan pie for dessert!  I ordered shrimp and grits- one of my favorite dishes.  Did not pay attention to the details of the dish because bbq sauce is used….. not my favorite way to have this dish.  Overall- 82 Queen is a great restaurant and I will go again.  I will just request my area of seating!</body>
      <date month="04" day="23" year="2015"/>
</review>
      <review type="user">
        <link>http://www.opentable.com/rest_profile_reviews.aspx?rid=16522&amp;ref=7312</link>
        <title>82 Queen - Charleston</title>
<author>OpenTable.com</author>

        <rating name="Ambience">5.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Food">5.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Noise">2.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Overall">5.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Service">5.000000000000000</rating>

        <body>MY wife and I tried the Brunch for the very first time and 82 Queen did not disappoint!   The Low-Country Omlet was succulent mixed with spinach and Gouda cheese! The coffee had that deep, rich aroma that partnered well with the Omlet! The ambiance at &quot;The Queen&quot; has always been our favorite in the Charleston area....filled with the period of a time of luxurious living before the Civil War! The wait-staff was very attentive.....and everyone wore a warm smile that projected the intent of a &quot;true welcome greeting&quot;!!! Definitely...one of...if not.... the BEST in Charleston!!!!</body>
      <date month="04" day="23" year="2015"/>
</review>
      <review type="user">
        <link>http://www.opentable.com/rest_profile_reviews.aspx?rid=16522&amp;ref=7312</link>
        <title>82 Queen - Charleston</title>
<author>OpenTable.com</author>

        <rating name="Ambience">4.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Food">5.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Noise">3.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Overall">5.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Service">5.000000000000000</rating>

        <body>We had a nice birthday dinner with wonderful scallops and she crab soup. Our friendly and knowledgeable waitress also recommended the &quot;Freak Show&quot; Cabernet and it is now one of our favourites. Will definitely return to this restaurant when we have the opportunity to visit Savannah again.</body>
      <date month="04" day="23" year="2015"/>
</review>
      <review type="user">
        <link>http://www.opentable.com/rest_profile_reviews.aspx?rid=16522&amp;ref=7312</link>
        <title>82 Queen - Charleston</title>
<author>OpenTable.com</author>

        <rating name="Ambience">5.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Food">5.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Noise">3.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Overall">5.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Service">5.000000000000000</rating>

        <body>Went for lunch for Restaurant Week. Decided on regular menu because of the selections. Service was great, Food excellent taste and presentation, reasonable price. Happy Hour bar was superb.</body>
      <date month="04" day="23" year="2015"/>
</review>
      <review type="user">
        <link>http://www.opentable.com/rest_profile_reviews.aspx?rid=16522&amp;ref=7312</link>
        <title>82 Queen - Charleston</title>
<author>OpenTable.com</author>

        <rating name="Ambience">2.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Food">1.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Noise">1.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Overall">1.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Service">1.000000000000000</rating>

        <body>It took two hours to eat lunch.  The food was very mediocre and the service was soooo slow!  I would not recommend this restaurant for lunch.</body>
      <date month="04" day="23" year="2015"/>
</review>
      <review type="user">
        <link>http://www.opentable.com/rest_profile_reviews.aspx?rid=16522&amp;ref=7312</link>
        <title>82 Queen - Charleston</title>
<author>OpenTable.com</author>

        <rating name="Ambience">5.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Food">4.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Noise">2.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Overall">5.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Service">5.000000000000000</rating>

        <body>We love 82 Queen. The setting in the courtyard is so pretty. All of our food was delicious. The hush puppies are amazing. Our service was excellent, helpful and friendly. The next time we want to try brunch.</body>
      <date month="04" day="23" year="2015"/>
</review>
      <review type="user">
        <link>http://www.opentable.com/rest_profile_reviews.aspx?rid=16522&amp;ref=7312</link>
        <title>82 Queen - Charleston</title>
<author>OpenTable.com</author>

        <rating name="Ambience">5.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Food">5.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Noise">1.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Overall">5.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Service">5.000000000000000</rating>

        <body>excellent!  Great food Great service! Mom&apos;s birthday and they really made her feel special  Too bad it was too cold to eat on the patio. A favorite spot for us.</body>
      <date month="04" day="23" year="2015"/>
</review>
      <review type="user">
        <link>http://www.opentable.com/rest_profile_reviews.aspx?rid=16522&amp;ref=7312</link>
        <title>82 Queen - Charleston</title>
<author>OpenTable.com</author>

        <rating name="Ambience">3.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Food">2.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Noise">2.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Overall">2.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Service">5.000000000000000</rating>

        <body>My husband and I went to Charleston for the Valentine&apos;s weekend.  Everyone, including our carriage tour guide,  said 82 Queen was the place to go.  Valentine&apos;s day the restaurant was fully booked so we made reservations for Sunday night.  After so much hype we were expecting the meal of our life.  We were thoroughly disappointed.  The famous &quot;she crab soup&quot; was inedible.  The famous &quot;shrimp and grits&quot; we not good at all.  The crab cake appetizer and the jambalaya were okay but not near what we expected from a restaurant of this caliber.  The biscuits were cold and so was our dining room.  This dinner was our big splurge for the weekend and I am sad to say it was not worth the time or the money.</body>
      <date month="04" day="23" year="2015"/>
</review>
      <review type="user">
        <link>http://www.opentable.com/rest_profile_reviews.aspx?rid=16522&amp;ref=7312</link>
        <title>82 Queen - Charleston</title>
<author>OpenTable.com</author>

        <rating name="Ambience">1.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Food">4.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Noise">1.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Overall">2.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Service">2.000000000000000</rating>

        <body>Sat at outside table next to gate connecting to bed &amp; breakfast. We began to smell a strong chlorine odor. At the same time my husband was being dripped on. We were sitting under a tree. We told our server the two issues   He chuckled as he said the Rose of Sharon drips as it blooms.  I&apos;ve checked with a couple of nurseries since &amp; they say they have never heard nor had the experience that that is true.  The dinner was not as special as we had hoped. We specifically chose 82 Queen over many other quality restaurants in the area because we had gone there on our 5th anniversary &amp; we were back in town 30 years later. Wish it had been different.</body>
      <date month="04" day="23" year="2015"/>
</review>
      <review type="user">
        <link>http://www.opentable.com/rest_profile_reviews.aspx?rid=16522&amp;ref=7312</link>
        <title>82 Queen - Charleston</title>
<author>OpenTable.com</author>

        <rating name="Ambience">4.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Food">5.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Noise">3.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Overall">4.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Service">4.000000000000000</rating>

        <body>This was our second time here, and it was every bit as good as the first.  In addition to the interesting menu and great food, the restaurant&apos;s layout is most unique. Built around a courtyard and a huge tree, you may be eating upstairs, inside, outside or sort of in-between, all of which are ok in any weather and add to the ambiance. You&apos;ll want to try their she crab soup; traditional but not ordinary.  Highly satisfied with service, food and ambiance.</body>
      <date month="04" day="23" year="2015"/>
</review>
      <review type="user">
        <link>http://www.opentable.com/rest_profile_reviews.aspx?rid=16522&amp;ref=7312</link>
        <title>82 Queen - Charleston</title>
<author>OpenTable.com</author>

        <rating name="Ambience">3.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Food">3.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Noise">2.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Overall">4.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Service">4.000000000000000</rating>

        <body>We made reservations at 82 Queen to celebrate my wife&apos;s birthday on a recent trip to Charleston, S.C.  Upon arriving at the restaurant, we were warmly greeted and escorted to an upper room (there are several such rooms, each with localized names).  Our waiter was handling about 4 other tables in the room that particular night and so the greeting and drink order was somewhat delayed.  After a relaxing and solitary time to enjoy our drinks, our orders were placed.  I had the she crab soup, which was very good.  My wife ordered the prime rib and I ordered the shrimp and grits.  Both dishes took an extra ordinary long  time to be presented to our table, given the fact this was a mid-week evening and the restaurant was sparsely occupied.  The food was very good, even though the prices were higher than I expected them to be.  All in all a very enjoyable evening but at a price that is in excess of the level of enjoyment.</body>
      <date month="04" day="23" year="2015"/>
</review>
      <review type="user">
        <link>http://www.opentable.com/rest_profile_reviews.aspx?rid=16522&amp;ref=7312</link>
        <title>82 Queen - Charleston</title>
<author>OpenTable.com</author>

        <rating name="Ambience">4.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Food">5.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Noise">1.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Overall">5.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Service">5.000000000000000</rating>

        <body>Never miss dining at 82 Queen when visiting Charleston, always a dining delight and pleasure for my taste buds , best BBQ shrimp and grits ever!!</body>
      <date month="04" day="23" year="2015"/>
</review>
      <review type="user">
        <link>http://www.opentable.com/rest_profile_reviews.aspx?rid=16522&amp;ref=7312</link>
        <title>82 Queen - Charleston</title>
<author>OpenTable.com</author>

        <rating name="Ambience">2.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Food">4.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Noise">3.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Overall">3.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Service">3.000000000000000</rating>

        <body>We have always loved the food at 82 Queen; however,on this occasion, two out of three of us were finished with our meal as the third was being served.  Add to this the fact that two in our party are handicapped and they could only accommodate us two flights up (with no apologies from the manager) we may have to rethink our next visit.  They didn&apos;t seem busy on the first floor, but the manager was firm that it was upstairs or we could not be accommodated.  She was not exhibiting the usual 82 Queen courtesy.  My favorite Charleston restaurant has disappointed me.</body>
      <date month="04" day="23" year="2015"/>
</review>
      <review type="user">
        <link>http://www.opentable.com/rest_profile_reviews.aspx?rid=16522&amp;ref=7312</link>
        <title>82 Queen - Charleston</title>
<author>OpenTable.com</author>

        <rating name="Ambience">4.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Food">5.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Noise">3.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Overall">4.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Service">5.000000000000000</rating>

        <body>This was the second time to dine at 82 Queen and was memorable in that we were the only diners in the entire dining room. We were told that the evening we were there is traditionally the slowest of the year. Food was very good, but a bit slow getting to us. Fun waiter who was very helpful. We would definitely go back, but hope for a more vibrant evening.</body>
      <date month="04" day="23" year="2015"/>
</review>
      <review type="user">
        <link>http://www.opentable.com/rest_profile_reviews.aspx?rid=16522&amp;ref=7312</link>
        <title>82 Queen - Charleston</title>
<author>OpenTable.com</author>

        <rating name="Ambience">3.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Food">3.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Noise">3.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Overall">3.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Service">4.000000000000000</rating>

        <body>We have eaten here several times in the past so we picked it for my wife&apos;s birthday celebration. The waiter recommended the Osco Buco, so we both ordered it from the Restaurant Week menu.  Mine was fall-apart perfect, but my wife&apos;s was very tough.  Since it was rather cool outside that evening, we did not send it back as it took more than 30 minutes to get the first entires. We switched plates and I tried to eat the tough meat, but it was not a good experience. We are going to count this as one bad experience, and we will return in warmer weather to try again.</body>
      <date month="04" day="23" year="2015"/>
</review>
      <review type="user">
        <link>http://www.opentable.com/rest_profile_reviews.aspx?rid=16522&amp;ref=7312</link>
        <title>82 Queen - Charleston</title>
<author>OpenTable.com</author>

        <rating name="Ambience">1.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Food">3.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Noise">1.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Overall">3.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Service">3.000000000000000</rating>

        <body>The host did not seat us at a very good spot even though the place was empty, there were some really nice  spots to seat,  to make our day more romantic. We got there early, we noticed only few customer, but they made us seat at the bar until the reservation time.</body>
      <date month="04" day="23" year="2015"/>
</review>
      <review type="user">
        <link>http://www.opentable.com/rest_profile_reviews.aspx?rid=16522&amp;ref=7312</link>
        <title>82 Queen - Charleston</title>
<author>OpenTable.com</author>

        <rating name="Ambience">4.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Food">2.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Noise">1.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Overall">3.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Service">5.000000000000000</rating>

        <body>The location was great for a pre theater dinner, and the service was wonderful and the atmosphere  in keeping with the neighborhood.  Alas, the food did not match the rest of the experience.  The she crab soup was just ok, and the fried pork chop had too much crust and was over cooked.</body>
      <date month="04" day="23" year="2015"/>
</review>
      <review type="user">
        <link>http://www.opentable.com/rest_profile_reviews.aspx?rid=16522&amp;ref=7312</link>
        <title>82 Queen - Charleston</title>
<author>OpenTable.com</author>

        <rating name="Ambience">5.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Food">5.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Noise">4.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Overall">5.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Service">5.000000000000000</rating>

        <body>We chose 82 Queen to celebrate my birthday and a good friend&apos;s birthday.  We ate here during Charleston Restaurant week which meant a fixed 3 course menu for $30.  The choices were excellent and the preparation was outstanding.  Our waiter was very attentive and well seasoned.  It was a wonderful evening with friends and a great place for our celebration.</body>
      <date month="04" day="23" year="2015"/>
</review>
      <review type="user">
        <link>http://www.opentable.com/rest_profile_reviews.aspx?rid=16522&amp;ref=7312</link>
        <title>82 Queen - Charleston</title>
<author>OpenTable.com</author>

        <rating name="Ambience">4.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Food">3.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Noise">1.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Overall">4.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Service">3.000000000000000</rating>

        <body>Had wanted to try 82 Queen for years..........was slightly disappointed.  Ambiance was lovely and service was good, although a little too fast paced for my liking.  While our food was truly very good, it was not outstanding nor was the presentation.  Would I go back? Yes, to try something different; but, I would try one of the other outstanding restaurants in Charleston first..</body>
      <date month="04" day="23" year="2015"/>
</review>
      <review type="user">
        <link>http://www.opentable.com/rest_profile_reviews.aspx?rid=16522&amp;ref=7312</link>
        <title>82 Queen - Charleston</title>
<author>OpenTable.com</author>

        <rating name="Ambience">5.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Food">5.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Noise">1.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Overall">5.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Service">5.000000000000000</rating>

        <body>82 Queen has great indoor and outdoor seating with a nice bar area. Perfect for dinner with friends or a romantic night out. Food was delicious and service was great.</body>
      <date month="04" day="23" year="2015"/>
</review>
      <review type="user">
        <link>http://www.opentable.com/rest_profile_reviews.aspx?rid=16522&amp;ref=7312</link>
        <title>82 Queen - Charleston</title>
<author>OpenTable.com</author>

        <rating name="Ambience">4.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Food">4.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Noise">3.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Overall">4.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Service">4.000000000000000</rating>

        <body>We were there for a week and didn&apos;t want to miss 82 Queen.  Since we hadn&apos;t had time for dinner we had a lovely lunch to send us on our way. Our waiter was tops. Thanks, we&apos;ll be back.</body>
      <date month="04" day="23" year="2015"/>
</review>
      <review type="user">
        <link>http://www.opentable.com/rest_profile_reviews.aspx?rid=16522&amp;ref=7312</link>
        <title>82 Queen - Charleston</title>
<author>OpenTable.com</author>

        <rating name="Ambience">4.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Food">5.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Noise">3.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Overall">5.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Service">5.000000000000000</rating>

        <body>Our waitress was extremely helpful and accommodating. We sat in this cute outdoor area (with heat lamps!) and enjoyed each other&apos;s company and the delicious food! I definitely recommend!</body>
      <date month="04" day="23" year="2015"/>
</review>
      <review type="user">
        <link>http://www.opentable.com/rest_profile_reviews.aspx?rid=16522&amp;ref=7312</link>
        <title>82 Queen - Charleston</title>
<author>OpenTable.com</author>

        <rating name="Ambience">4.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Food">4.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Noise">2.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Overall">4.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Service">5.000000000000000</rating>

        <body>We had visitors in town from Chicago. No problem for us to showcase Charleston against Chicago restaurants. We were professionally served and our guests were quite pleased with both the quality of the food and the presentation. Its a go to spot for us and our visitors from off.</body>
      <date month="04" day="23" year="2015"/>
</review>
      <review type="user">
        <link>http://www.opentable.com/rest_profile_reviews.aspx?rid=16522&amp;ref=7312</link>
        <title>82 Queen - Charleston</title>
<author>OpenTable.com</author>

        <rating name="Ambience">5.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Food">4.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Noise">1.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Overall">5.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Service">5.000000000000000</rating>

        <body>We found 82 Queen on Open Table and the reviews made us want to come . They were right! The restaurant is a lovely, quaint, elegant setting combining charming indoor dining rooms and delightful outdoor (but sheltered) patio tables. The wait staff was very attentive and helpful to our group of seven, and almost everything was perfect. I say almost everything because one chicken dish came out undercooked; it was quickly replaced with a comped entree and generous apologies.  The barbecue shrimp and grits, the she-crab soup, the fried green tomatoes, the hush puppies, the jambalaya... all were excellent. The cocktails were also delicious, and the wine selection was quite good. We should have saved more room for dessert! As it was, we ordered one piece of bourbon pecan pie and passed it around the table so everyone could have a bite. Heavenly!  This is a terrific special occasion restaurant, and definitely romantic. I&apos;m sure they&apos;ve seen more than their fair share of proposals! We will be </body>
      <date month="04" day="23" year="2015"/>
</review>
      <review type="user">
        <link>http://www.opentable.com/rest_profile_reviews.aspx?rid=16522&amp;ref=7312</link>
        <title>82 Queen - Charleston</title>
<author>OpenTable.com</author>

        <rating name="Ambience">5.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Food">5.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Noise">4.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Overall">5.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Service">5.000000000000000</rating>

        <body>82 Queen never fails to amaze us. We specifically went to Charleston to eat here. The she-crab soup is crave worthy and my husband said his shrimp and grits was the best he&apos;s had. The outdoor seating is amazing, even in cool weather. The staff is fun and knowledgable. It&apos;s a great find. It has a unique setting and the food is so good, you&apos;ll want to bring your friends!</body>
      <date month="04" day="23" year="2015"/>
</review>
      <review type="user">
        <link>http://www.opentable.com/rest_profile_reviews.aspx?rid=16522&amp;ref=7312</link>
        <title>82 Queen - Charleston</title>
<author>OpenTable.com</author>

        <rating name="Ambience">5.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Food">5.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Noise">3.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Overall">5.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Service">5.000000000000000</rating>

        <body>A reservation for an early dinner on Christmas Eve was confirmed by phone the day before, which is unusual. As our meal progressed the reason for the call was apparent; the restaurant became packed, but with no fuss. The service was excellent, exceptionally professional and friendly. We both had grouper that was perfectly prepared.  It was served on a bed of succatash garnished with fried okra.   The entire meal experience was outstanding and was topped off by attending a Christmas Eve service at St. Philips.</body>
      <date month="04" day="23" year="2015"/>
</review>
      <review type="user">
        <link>http://www.opentable.com/rest_profile_reviews.aspx?rid=16522&amp;ref=7312</link>
        <title>82 Queen - Charleston</title>
<author>OpenTable.com</author>

        <rating name="Ambience">4.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Food">4.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Noise">4.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Overall">4.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Service">4.000000000000000</rating>

        <body>It was a cold night in Charleston and the hostess accommodated our request not to sit in a makeshift outdoor room warmed by a space heater.  We had to wait a few minutes past our 6:30 reservation but were given a lovely corner table with a view of Queen Street in a small room.   We ordered from the  restaurant week menu. Three out of four opted for she crab soup and the peppercorn filet. #4 had the picklin&apos; plate and pork osso buco.   Two out of three steaks were done as requested; the osso buco was falling off the bone and tasty with collards, garlic mashed potatoes and carrots.  Desserts were first rate. The noise level was more than moderate with a group of women sitting behind us. Service was excellent and professional. The pace was good and we weren&apos;t rushed. Glad to have used Open Table when I heard hostess turning away walk-ins with next tables available at 9:30.</body>
      <date month="04" day="23" year="2015"/>
</review>
      <review type="user">
        <link>http://www.opentable.com/rest_profile_reviews.aspx?rid=16522&amp;ref=7312</link>
        <title>82 Queen - Charleston</title>
<author>OpenTable.com</author>

        <rating name="Ambience">3.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Food">5.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Noise">1.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Overall">4.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Service">5.000000000000000</rating>

        <body>We went on a Thursday night, so maybe that&apos;s why it was so quiet (which is nice) but I also like a great ambience to go with my food to create a great dining experience. The service was great and so was the food, so overall it was awesome! The BBQ Shrimp and Grits are amazing!</body>
      <date month="04" day="23" year="2015"/>
</review>
      <review type="user">
        <link>http://www.opentable.com/rest_profile_reviews.aspx?rid=16522&amp;ref=7312</link>
        <title>82 Queen - Charleston</title>
<author>OpenTable.com</author>

        <rating name="Ambience">5.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Food">1.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Noise">1.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Overall">3.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Service">3.000000000000000</rating>

        <body>We have been to 82 Queen every visit to Charleston over the past 20 years. This time was our last. When the waitress served our appetizers she said this must be the all carb table. That got us a look from the next table. When my meal came it was missing the gravy that is with the chicken and the brussel sprouts were so hard I could not get a fork in them. When we told her she said she was bringing the manager out. I said don&apos;t bring them just take it off the bill which she DID NOT do. Very disappointed in the experience and the service has gone down hill this much.</body>
      <date month="04" day="23" year="2015"/>
</review>
      <review type="user">
        <link>http://www.opentable.com/rest_profile_reviews.aspx?rid=16522&amp;ref=7312</link>
        <title>82 Queen - Charleston</title>
<author>OpenTable.com</author>

        <rating name="Ambience">4.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Food">2.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Noise">2.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Overall">4.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Service">4.000000000000000</rating>

        <body>I had heard about this restaurant from some friends, and let me say upfront I am not a seafood eater. I ordered the hamburger that came with a fried egg and bacon. I ordered it well done. It came out VERY pink. I should have sent it back, but I don&apos;t like to make a fuss, so I tried to eat it. Not successful. My dining partner had the crabcake BLT. and she was underwhelmed. She said she would just go for the she crab soup, and be very happy.</body>
      <date month="04" day="23" year="2015"/>
</review>
      <review type="user">
        <link>http://www.opentable.com/rest_profile_reviews.aspx?rid=16522&amp;ref=7312</link>
        <title>82 Queen - Charleston</title>
<author>OpenTable.com</author>

        <rating name="Ambience">3.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Food">3.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Noise">4.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Overall">3.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Service">4.000000000000000</rating>

        <body>We went here for the $30 three-course meal that was promoted during &quot;Restaurant week&quot;.  The soup was excellent.  The dessert was excellent. The entrée was only OK.  I ordered the Peppercorn Encrusted Filet Mignon.  The filet was cooked to perfection.  I didn&apos;t care for the peppercorn, but I should have known that going in.  However, the sides provided were three of the thinnest asparagus you will ever see and Inedible &quot;confit fingerling potatoes&quot;. They were hard as a rock.  I would have preferred a hearty dose of the garlic mashed potatoes that accompanied another entrée.  I don&apos;t understand the logic in serving these &quot;chips&quot; with a perfectly prepared steak.  The service was excellent.  The place was nice.</body>
      <date month="04" day="23" year="2015"/>
</review>
      <review type="user">
        <link>http://www.opentable.com/rest_profile_reviews.aspx?rid=16522&amp;ref=7312</link>
        <title>82 Queen - Charleston</title>
<author>OpenTable.com</author>

        <rating name="Ambience">5.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Food">5.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Noise">1.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Overall">4.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Service">5.000000000000000</rating>

        <body>Great location and nice atmosphere. Good food and friendly service.</body>
      <date month="04" day="23" year="2015"/>
</review>
      <review type="user">
        <link>http://www.opentable.com/rest_profile_reviews.aspx?rid=16522&amp;ref=7312</link>
        <title>82 Queen - Charleston</title>
<author>OpenTable.com</author>

        <rating name="Ambience">5.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Food">3.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Noise">1.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Overall">5.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Service">5.000000000000000</rating>

        <body>The restaurant was nice but some of my friends didn&apos;t like their food. This restaurant is for people who have a certain taste for the type of food that they serve. I played it safe and ordered a salad. However, the atmosphere is nice and so was the staff.</body>
      <date month="04" day="23" year="2015"/>
</review>
      <review type="user">
        <link>http://www.opentable.com/rest_profile_reviews.aspx?rid=16522&amp;ref=7312</link>
        <title>82 Queen - Charleston</title>
<author>OpenTable.com</author>

        <rating name="Ambience">4.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Food">1.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Noise">1.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Overall">2.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Service">3.000000000000000</rating>

        <body>This restaurant was a real disappointment. While the ambiance was quite nice with a series of small dining rooms, the menu was uninteresting. The signature dish of BBQ Shrimp and grits tasted as if it had been prepared weeks ago. Service was adequate although in my opinion a restaurant of this caliber should get the right orders to the customers on the first try. Also I was surprised that in this day and age there was no espresso machine.  I would not recommend this restaurant to anyone. There are many better choices in Charleston.</body>
      <date month="04" day="23" year="2015"/>
</review>
      <review type="user">
        <link>http://www.opentable.com/rest_profile_reviews.aspx?rid=16522&amp;ref=7312</link>
        <title>82 Queen - Charleston</title>
<author>OpenTable.com</author>

        <rating name="Ambience">5.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Food">5.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Noise">3.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Overall">5.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Service">5.000000000000000</rating>

        <body>We were in awe as we first walked in by the pure beauty of the place. From patio seating with outdoor heaters to the upstairs dining area, where we ended up had such a wonderful ambiance. The She crab soup was delicious! The best crab cakes that I have ever tasted! The staff was completely knowledgeable about the dishes and helped with our food choices. The staff was extremely attentive and classy in every way. We ended our dinner with a chocolate cheesecake which was just as divine as the rest of our meal. We will definitely be returning customers of 82 Queen!</body>
      <date month="04" day="23" year="2015"/>
</review>
      <review type="user">
        <link>http://www.opentable.com/rest_profile_reviews.aspx?rid=16522&amp;ref=7312</link>
        <title>82 Queen - Charleston</title>
<author>OpenTable.com</author>

        <rating name="Ambience">3.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Food">3.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Noise">1.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Overall">3.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Service">3.000000000000000</rating>

        <body>WE were seated promptly for Sunday brunch. The outside area is beautiful. The inside is fine. Our meal arrived within seconds of our drinks. The waiter was constantly removing dishes while others were eating. He even brought dessert menus when someone was finishing their meal. The food was very average compared to other brunches in the city.</body>
      <date month="04" day="23" year="2015"/>
</review>
      <review type="user">
        <link>http://www.opentable.com/rest_profile_reviews.aspx?rid=16522&amp;ref=7312</link>
        <title>82 Queen - Charleston</title>
<author>OpenTable.com</author>

        <rating name="Ambience">5.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Food">5.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Noise">1.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Overall">5.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Service">5.000000000000000</rating>

        <body>Their barbecue shrimp and grits was a dish to die for.  It looked great and tasted great unlike the same dish we had at SNOB a night before, which was totally tasteless.  Jambalaya could have been better., and it was more or less on dry side., however. The outdoor setting on a beautiful spring sunny day mad our lunch more enjoyable and memorable.</body>
      <date month="04" day="23" year="2015"/>
</review>
      <review type="user">
        <link>http://www.opentable.com/rest_profile_reviews.aspx?rid=16522&amp;ref=7312</link>
        <title>82 Queen - Charleston</title>
<author>OpenTable.com</author>

        <rating name="Ambience">4.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Food">4.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Noise">1.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Overall">4.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Service">5.000000000000000</rating>

        <body>We have eaten here on three or four occasions over the last two years. The food is consistently good. She-crab soup is the best and the rest follows suit. The staff&apos;s effort and motivation to please is obvious.</body>
      <date month="04" day="23" year="2015"/>
</review>
      <review type="user">
        <link>http://www.opentable.com/rest_profile_reviews.aspx?rid=16522&amp;ref=7312</link>
        <title>82 Queen - Charleston</title>
<author>OpenTable.com</author>

        <rating name="Ambience">5.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Food">3.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Noise">4.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Overall">3.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Service">4.000000000000000</rating>

        <body>We always eat here when we travel to Charleston for sentimental reasons, have been going here for over 20 years. I love the outdoor setting, which on a cold night is supplemented with heaters. Very beautiful and romantic atmosphere. Our food this vista was not exceptional, the soup special of tomato/ artichoke was not very palatable and the mahi with lemon butter sauce was well cooked, however the sauce was just a pool of melted butter that did not enhance the flavor of the fish at all.  However, we will be back next visit to the area and hope that this was just a blip on an otherwise lovely dining destination.</body>
      <date month="04" day="23" year="2015"/>
</review>
      <review type="user">
        <link>http://www.opentable.com/rest_profile_reviews.aspx?rid=16522&amp;ref=7312</link>
        <title>82 Queen - Charleston</title>
<author>OpenTable.com</author>

        <rating name="Ambience">5.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Food">4.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Noise">1.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Overall">5.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Service">5.000000000000000</rating>

        <body>Great Charleston Experience! The layout is very unique.  The service was great! Try the She-Crab Soup.  Excellent Choice for Low Country Cuisine!</body>
      <date month="04" day="23" year="2015"/>
</review>
      <review type="user">
        <link>http://www.opentable.com/rest_profile_reviews.aspx?rid=16522&amp;ref=7312</link>
        <title>82 Queen - Charleston</title>
<author>OpenTable.com</author>

        <rating name="Ambience">5.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Food">5.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Noise">2.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Overall">5.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Service">5.000000000000000</rating>

        <body>The She-Crab soup and Shrimp and Grits were fabulous! Would love to try everything on the menu.</body>
      <date month="04" day="23" year="2015"/>
</review>
      <review type="user">
        <link>http://www.opentable.com/rest_profile_reviews.aspx?rid=16522&amp;ref=7312</link>
        <title>82 Queen - Charleston</title>
<author>OpenTable.com</author>

        <rating name="Ambience">3.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Food">1.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Noise">1.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Overall">2.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Service">2.000000000000000</rating>

        <body>The service was slow, even though we intentionally made an early reservation and informed the wait staff that we had to be out by a certain time for a concert.  Then when we had to send back one of the entrees back because it was grossly overcooked to the point of being burnt,  we were late for the concert and my husband was able to eat only half of the replacement entree.  This made the entire dining experience at 82 Queen much less than satisfactory.</body>
      <date month="04" day="23" year="2015"/>
</review>
      <review type="user">
        <link>http://www.opentable.com/rest_profile_reviews.aspx?rid=16522&amp;ref=7312</link>
        <title>82 Queen - Charleston</title>
<author>OpenTable.com</author>

        <rating name="Ambience">2.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Food">1.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Noise">3.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Overall">1.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Service">2.000000000000000</rating>

        <body>It was restaurant week and we hoped to be able to go to a very nice place like 82Queen for a reasonable price ($30 each for fixed/limited 3 course).  First our table was in the back upstairs, but by a cold door - every time someone entered there was a blast of cold air.  The She Crab soup was fishy, the Chicken gumbo as ok, but on the cold side.  Shrimp and Grits was nothing to write home about (we had Shrimp and Grits at Pearlz the night before and THEY were spectacular).  The Jambalaya - was ok, but too heavy on tomato  and frankly I make better at home.  Desserts were ok, but they waiter did not even ask if we wanted coffee.  Wine was very pricy - overpriced even for a fancy restaurant.  It cost almost as much as our meals for 2 and that was a low end wine.    Some other guests we met at the Elliot Inn we stayed at (next door to 82Queen) has suggested Magnolia&apos;s - we wish we had gone there instead.  Very disappointed with 82Queen.</body>
      <date month="04" day="23" year="2015"/>
</review>
      <review type="user">
        <link>http://www.opentable.com/rest_profile_reviews.aspx?rid=16522&amp;ref=7312</link>
        <title>82 Queen - Charleston</title>
<author>OpenTable.com</author>

        <rating name="Ambience">3.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Food">3.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Noise">1.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Overall">3.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Service">4.000000000000000</rating>

        <body>We had the she crab soup and Jambalaya.  The soup was a bit disappointing.  The Jambalya was delicious despite the overcooked and hard pieces of ham.  There were plenty od shrimp and crawfish to make up for that.</body>
      <date month="04" day="23" year="2015"/>
</review>
      <review type="user">
        <link>http://www.opentable.com/rest_profile_reviews.aspx?rid=16522&amp;ref=7312</link>
        <title>82 Queen - Charleston</title>
<author>OpenTable.com</author>

        <rating name="Ambience">5.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Food">3.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Noise">1.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Overall">4.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Service">3.000000000000000</rating>

        <body>Decent food. I got the surf and turf which was very tasty. I would recommend getting a southern dish there instead. Halls or Oak definitely make a better steak. They were also out of 2 out of the 3 bottles of wine we requested.</body>
      <date month="04" day="23" year="2015"/>
</review>
      <review type="user">
        <link>http://www.opentable.com/rest_profile_reviews.aspx?rid=16522&amp;ref=7312</link>
        <title>82 Queen - Charleston</title>
<author>OpenTable.com</author>

        <rating name="Ambience">4.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Food">5.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Noise">3.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Overall">5.000000000000000</rating>
        <rating name="Service">5.000000000000000</rating>

        <body>Wow, this restaurant was way more than expected. It was one of the best! Put this one on your list. I can&apos;t begin to tell you how great the food and service was.</body>
      <date month="04" day="23" year="2015"/>
</review>

      <image type="photo" url="http://www.opentable.com/img/restimages/16522.jpg" width="195" height="200">
        <link>http://www.opentable.com/rest_profile.aspx?rid=16522&amp;ref=7312</link>
        <title>82 Queen - Charleston</title>
<author>OpenTable.com</author>
      <date month="04" day="23" year="2015"/>
</image>

      <attributes>
        <link>http://www.opentable.com/rest_profile.aspx?rid=16522&amp;ref=7312</link>
        <title>82 Queen Details</title>
<author>OpenTable.com</author>
        <website>www.82Queen.com</website>

        <attr name="Additional Info">Banquet/Private Rooms</attr>
        <attr name="Additional Info">Bar Dining</attr>
        <attr name="Additional Info">Bar/Lounge</attr>
        <attr name="Additional Info">Beer</attr>
        <attr name="Additional Info">Counter Seating</attr>
        <attr name="Additional Info">Farm to Table</attr>
        <attr name="Additional Info">Fireplace</attr>
        <attr name="Additional Info">Full Bar</attr>
        <attr name="Additional Info">Gluten-free Menu</attr>
        <attr name="Additional Info">Happy Hour</attr>
        <attr name="Additional Info">Non-Smoking Restaurant</attr>
        <attr name="Additional Info">Patio/Outdoor Dining</attr>
        <attr name="Additional Info">Personal wines welcome</attr>
        <attr name="Additional Info">Personal wines welcome (corkage fee applies)</attr>
        <attr name="Additional Info">Private Room</attr>
        <attr name="Additional Info">Takeout</attr>
        <attr name="Additional Info">Weekend Brunch</attr>
        <attr name="Additional Info">Wheelchair Access</attr>
        <attr name="Additional Info">Wine</attr>
        <attr name="Cross Street">King &amp; Meeting</attr>
        <attr name="Dining Style">Fine Dining</attr>
        <attr name="Dress Code">Business Casual</attr>
        <attr name="Executive Chef">Nick Ingram</attr>
        <attr name="Neighborhood">Downtown Charleston</attr>
        <attr name="Parking Options">Public Lot</attr>
        <attr name="Payment accepted">AMEX</attr>
        <attr name="Payment accepted">Discover</attr>
        <attr name="Payment accepted">MasterCard</attr>
        <attr name="Payment accepted">Visa</attr>
        <attr name="Price Quartile">$$</attr>
        <attr name="Reservation">http://www.opentable.com/rest_profile.aspx?rid=16522&amp;ref=7312</attr>
        <attr name="Tip Policy">1%</attr>
        <attr name="Walkins Accepted">Yes</attr>
      <date month="04" day="23" year="2015"/>
</attributes>
    </content>
  </listing>
 </listings>